[
    {
        "front": "いま",
        "back": "今 \nNow",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "こんげつ",
        "back": "今月 \nThis month",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "ことし",
        "back": "今年 \nThis year",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "きょう",
        "back": "今日 \nToday",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "あう",
        "back": "会う \nTo meet",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいわ",
        "back": "会話 \nConversation",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃかい",
        "back": "社会 \nSociety",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "かいしゃ",
        "back": "会社 \nCompany",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しゃちょう",
        "back": "社長 \npresident",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "みせ",
        "back": "店 \nShop",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "えき",
        "back": "駅 \nStation",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "はな",
        "back": "花 \nFlower",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "くに",
        "back": "国 \nCountry, nation",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "がいこく",
        "back": "外国 \nForeigh country",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "しろい",
        "back": "白い \nWhite",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "そら",
        "back": "空 \nSky",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "くうき",
        "back": "空気 \nAir",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "おおぞら",
        "back": "大空 \nBig sky",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんしゃ",
        "back": "電車 \nTrain",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんわ",
        "back": "電話 \ntelephone",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    },
    {
        "front": "でんき",
        "back": "電気 \nElectricity, light",
        "chapter": "N5 K11"
    }
]